dailyinterlake.com 2017-05-19

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order
for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of
personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.
        • Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the
       purposes for which information is being collected.
        • We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of
       fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes,
       unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
        • We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment
       of those purposes.
        • We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where
       appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
        • Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used,
       and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete,
       and up-to-date.
        • We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against
       loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or
       modification.
        • We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and
       practices relating to the management of personal information.
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in
order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and
maintained.
